company has posted the number of landing applicants who want to set up the song. Brokerage
houses are assuming that some report has
come but then Tiger Shroff is above the tape and at 379
and there is an outperform rating and neither has it been
clarified that the numbers are much better
and the education part has been seen to be very strong. The
deal pipeline of the company is
better. Apart from this, the company is planning to increase its inputs
in the Owaisi sector of Hisar, which is
very from home. His wife's input cost of
his art has increased, which has an impact
on the margin of the company. The
deal pipeline will continue to
remain within their first
half. Jyoti will
get the second fiddle after one deal pipeline in the first half and this is
looking good. The performance rating of this large company is looking good
and the target is for the bottom of
₹300. They have seen a good rise
but according to them, stay in the price. ₹300. If you are
taking out the sponge, then remember to write on the box,
both types are going right now. The view on some sides is
very high, some
SEBI is posting it but  There is a lot of
posting, there
is a report from Mainpuri, regarding this potato matter,
they believe that 1045 kits out of 1048 can be
seen, if there is
pain in the underperform rating, then see from here also, they felt
that ₹500 worth of dance and staff can be seen in the office,
according to them, the
number of joins is below the estimate, in terms of
percentage, the situation that is developing now is
not sustainable to a great extent, going forward, there
seems to be a little more doubt, Sursingh is bigger, whose
vaccine's profitability, Pintu and
valuation, this is the condition which they have
raised first, the CLSA report has
said target 17, but their relatives have been
cut and the firms have reduced the rating from the back side and given
underperform rating, so there
is a cut in the rating even though the targets are coming above them,
apart from this, they also
gave commentary on the website that the numbers are below Hanuman, the
valuation part is very expensive, due to this, it will
not be able to do going forward, more percentage,
it is performing well, but the  There
is a valuation part, due to which
they
knocked it from buy and performed, so that is why
those numbers were considered fine by putting it on hold but the
quick comment is definitely on the website and everyone is
seeing the valuation part Jorgensen,
here you are getting great results and there will
definitely be upgrades, so keeping this in mind,
everyone should assume that
Tiles can give very good numbers on a standalone basis,
consolidated, so what you have said is a
matter of later, but on a standalone basis, the
numbers can give a very strong definition,
you have a Morgan Stanley report,
Tata Steel has an overweight rating of
840, the author is Jeffrey Script, the target is 850 on the back side,
in both the reports, it was
clear that Tata Steel, BSL, Tata
Metaliks, their numbers are very strong and
these numbers are time-sensitive, actually
controversies were seen on the numbers of U3, there is a
surprise in relation to this,
6 from these companies, along with the best
margin companies have posted that
picture, you will have to show that and by reducing the company update, they were
also saying things, this
sector  This is very positive for this company.
Jeffries believes that the
10% reduction in Shell Poly is also said to be a
going forward impact
or not.
Shravan is positive about this. The company's numbers are poor, the
sales volume is poor but the
realization has increased by 20%, so
their margins have become more important, and the
biggest thing is that its numbers are
good, hence Tata Steel's numbers
can also be good and in view of this,
their target
is around 40850.